BGM
So, I'd like to do 100 questions.
I would like to do 100 questions.
Yay!
I'm looking forward to hearing from you!
Self introduction
Yes, I am Yuna Tsukuki from Miyake Prefecture.
My member color is blue.
My nicknames are Yuna and Yuna-chan.
My birthday is September 15, 2002. I will be 21 this year.
What are you doing on the day the world ends?
Let's see...
I'm going to eat out at my favorite restaurant.
I'm going to take out
I'll be eating there for the rest of my life.
Definitely something.
What kind of yakitori do you want?
Skin.
SpongeBob
Sasane gizzards
Yakitori with sauce or salt?
Wow!
Both.
Salt, some salt
I take white streaks of mandarin oranges.
I do, but not when I'm really tired.
Basically, I take them off.
What is your favorite hairstyle?
Well, I like ponytails, so I often wear a ponytail on days of live performances.
I love spicy food. If I were to dye my hair, what color would it be?
I want to try pink.
TrustBelieveI don't want to believe, but I do.
My personal #1 rice accompaniment is natto (fermented soybeans)!
I had cold yakko yesterday, the one that wasn't coarse, the one that wasn't coarse, the one that wasn't coarse, the one that wasn't coarse, the one that wasn't coarse, the one that wasn't coarse...
Oh, silk, silk, silk!
How many ramen noodles can you eat?How many ramen noodles can you eat?
I want you to do this for a project.
I want to do this!
But definitely...
I can definitely have two bowls of ramen. Two bowls of kaedama.
Or three.
I think I can do it.
I'd like to go for 5.
What do you need for the expedition? I think I can make it. I want to go for go.
What do you need for an expedition? a. I'll bring skin care and shampoo.
If I'm in a band, I'd like to play the drums as much as possible.
I eat grilled food by peeling the skin off.
What is the dream you had recently?
The dream I had recently was...
I don't know...
The most...
I dreamed that someone I met that day
I dreamed that I was chased by someone I met that day.
My favorite season is
When the temperature is just right before summer.
Rice or bread? Bread? Bread!
Bread!
What flavor of ramen do you prefer? Pork bone broth.
Black mayo would be nice.
Lifetime Transportation Free Door to Anywhere
Um... Anywhere door.
What do you like in the picture?
Salmon is my favorite.
I also like hamachi.
Well...
I like hamachi, and I like shrimp.
I also like sea urchin.
I like negitoro.
I like them all.
If you can figure it out, what would you like?
Oh, right.It was.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know,
Oh, hmm.
Like Yuko Oshimada.
If you could figure out the name of the group, what would it be?
What?
A group name... something short.
Like "Tonkatsu" or "pork cutlet".
Something easy to say.
What's your favorite word?
Well... what's your favorite word?
Favorite word?
I can manage.
Where would you like to travel in Japan?
Ishikawa, Mie and Okinawa.
Any overseas trips? Right now I really want to go to Hawaii.
I want to eat acai balls all the time!
Hawaii!
What do you do on your days off?
Basically, I go out to eat with friends.
I also go shopping by myself.
But there are rare days when I just sleep.
How many meals a day do you eat?
When I am with Mr. Tohoku, I eat breakfast.
When I am not with Mr. Tohoku, I don't eat breakfast.
What is your favorite animal?
Hmmm...
Goldfish.
Favorite lyrics and song?
mmm
and
What are your favorite lyrics and favorite songs by Airi Suzuki?
Hmmm...umm...all the songs that Airi Suzuki singsUm, um, um, all the songs that Airi Suzuki sings.
What is your favorite English word?
Um... happy.
Do you have a driver's license?
Yes, I do.
I'm going to get a paper license.
How fast are you at 50 meters?
The latest I can remember is 8.6 or something like that.
I'm very slow.
What's your favorite subject?
Math until I was in junior high school.
Home economics in high school.
ShynessI'm probably not shy.
I can probably go out to dinner with anyone.
My boom is "Asahi Balls".
If I go to Tokyo, I'll definitely eat them.
I also eat them in Miyagi.
If you were to compare yourself with one kanji character
I have waves, so if I were to compare myself with one kanji character, I would say "Wave".
I have waves.
I have
The highest voice I can make
What is your favorite Tohoku song? Right now I like the song from episode 2 the best. It's really fun.
What do you think about during a live performance?
Well, really, um, except when we are not doing a big show, I am completely relaxed, so all I can think about is having fun.
What is the most fun song to sing live?
I haven't sung it yet, but Tequina is fun.
But I think I might have gotten an update after 2 episodes.
Episode 2 is very good!
What is your favorite nabe dish?
Ito konnyaku
What is your favorite oden ingredient? I've never had oden.
Oden...
I've never had oden in my 20 years of life.
I'm sorry.
Who do you admire?Who do you admire?
Who do you admire?
I admire Airi Suzuki right now.
If you could take one thing with you to a desert island, what would it be? I admire Airi Suzuki right now.
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be?
A cup noodle set that looks like a cup noodle set.
If you were to go to a deserted island, who would you take with you?
If you were going to go to a deserted island, who would you take with you?
Mew? I think he would lighten the mood.
If you could switch places with any member, who would it be? I'd like to be Lung-chan, wouldn't you?
I'd like to take a peek inside your brain.
If you were a man, who would you like to date? I'd like to take a peek inside Lun-chan's brain.
If you were a man, which member would you like to date?
No, I don't.
What sport would you like to play? I want to be able to play basketball.
I also like baseball.
If I could be the best dancer in the world, I'd want to play baseball and basketball.
I'd be the best dancer in the world and the best singer in the world.
But if I wasn't who I am now, if I were someone else, I'd want to be a better dancer, but I'd want to be a better singer.
But if I were someone else, I'd want to be better at dancing, but I'd want to be better at dancing, but I'd want to be better at singing.
Which is it?
I'd like to never gain weight in my life... and I'd like you to create that world for me.
What would you like to say to the non-believers?
Oh, I'm a nikka already!
I think it's a great thing to be a follower.
I think it's a very good thing.
I think it's a great thing.
I'm not going to let you down.
I'm not going to let you beat me.
I'm not losing.
A song you'd recommend to a complete stranger? I don't think you're an expert.
If I knew Neutron, I'd be wowed.
Depends on the day a lot... if we're wearing each other's clothes, I'll go "wow"!
Depends on the day a lot. Depends on the day a lot.
I'm not talking about pajamas, I'm talking about a jersey and a sweatshirt or a T-shirt or something. T-shirt?I'm not wearing pajamas, I'm wearing a jersey and a sweatshirt or a T-shirt. T-shirt?
We don't wear pajamas.
Urban, urban.
Wow, gold.
What?
What are they?
Shoes? Shoes, maybe? A wallet?
I'm not sure. Food.
You know, I've been to that haunted place on youtube.
Well... well... you've been there, haven't you?
I know you have.
I like natto rolls.
If it's onigiri...
I want to eat bonito flakes...
Bonito flakes.
What kind of entertainment work would you like to do?
I'd like to do a very cheerful MC position.
Very cheerful, like a festival.
Watermelon?
Watermelon? I'm sorry.
I don't even remember eating watermelon.
Is that what you believed when you were little?
I thought whales didn't exist.
How many questions?
I was really shy when I was little, and I couldn't stand up in front of people, even at piano recitals.
Even at piano recitals, she would sit in the piano chair and not play for a long time, and then she'd be dismissed.
I was 10 in the water group. The exact opposite. MIZUHA
But something real, but something like...
I want to play songs that don't make sense. Me too. Like, "What is this? I've been thinking about it for a long time. I've been thinking about it for a long time.
Yes, I'd like to make a song that adds a lot of unexpected effects.
I'll make a box for each occasion.
There are a lot of Showa-era songs.
I'm definitely jumping around.
Squash Time
Eh, I'm already talking all the time, mostly talking.
I sleep only when I'm extremely tired.I only sleep when I'm extremely tired.
I was in a ballet club for a year where we only ordered iced tea, unsweetened iced tea.
You're not sure if I'd call it that.
What's the hardest piece?
Hard music?
Hard music? The hard ones.
I've been struggling with Tenichi and Wonderful for the past few years.
I might have struggled with them all these years.
I've been doing it for a long time.
Yeah...
It's in a high key.
How did you get into show business?
My father was interested in the arts.
He found a piece of paper.
He found a sheet of paper with an audition on it.
I auditioned.
Q. Why did you audition?
I believe in it!
I believe in fate.
I believe that it is fate that I am here.
Q. Who are your friends?
Who is your favorite friend?
I'm here!
Well, Aya Nakamachi and the Nakamachi brothers,
I've been watching Aya Nakamachi, the Nakamachi Brothers, Towa-san, and Yuka Furukawa for a long time.
I also watch a lot of the new generation of youtubers.
Please collaborate with us!
What were you addicted to when you were little?
Learning.
What is your favorite thing about yourself?
Myself.
Tell me what is your favorite thing about yourself in everyday life.
I'm the same person I am in everyday life as I am in a talk show.
I'm almost the same as I am in a talk show.I'm almost the same.
I think it's kind of easy to talk to you.
Yes, next.
My hobbies are visiting good restaurants, going to good restaurants, looking for good restaurants, and talking to people.
Do you confess your feelings to someone? Or do you wait?
I definitely wait. I don't think girls can do that.
Are you a good swimmer?
I can't swim. I can't do sports.
Where would you like to go with the group?
Uh... uh... uh... Nagano or...
Maybe in Karuizawa.
I'd like to stay in a cottage with a view of the stars.
I'd like to stay there.
Western food?
But Japanese food also depends on my mood.
Well, well, well, well...
Rakuten Stadium.
Like Dekar.
How would you describe your animal? What? What's that? What's that?
Tiger or something like that?
It's hard to compare each member to an animal!
Let's see, Lun-chan, you're a rabbit.
Rine is a cat, right?
But you know, Rene looks like a cat.
But considering the part about sticking together, I'd say that a human being could be a cat.
I don't know... I don't know... I don't know.
What kind of animal is a smart animal that has a good lifestyle and is very disciplined? What's a smart animal that's well-rounded?
I'd say a monkey.
I don't know.
They wake up early, don't they?
Next, pearls.
Pearls.
Pearls are surprisingly...
Pearls are...
In a good way, they're kind of random.
I wonder what it is.I wonder what it is.
Panda.
Karen, Karen... panda... Karen...
Karen, I don't feel good.
Karen's a cat.
Maybe Karen is the cat.
Next.
Hi, Mon.
Oh, my God.
You're a dog.
A dog.
What's friendlier than a dog?
Then a dog
Double dog.
Let's see...
Next, Miu Miu.
I wonder if Mew has any interesting animals.
Something funny.
I think I'll get a donkey or something.
Sounds fun.
Kaya.
Kaya is... pretty... reliable.
Surprisingly...
She's surprisingly reliable.
Lion
Yes, Lion.
In a word, what is your selling point, Mr. Tork?
Well...
He is honest, for better or worse.
Singer you would like to perform opposite
I've never had a face-off with a Halo Pro group, so I'd like to.
I have a lot of ideas.
I definitely want to work at a cafe with a green logo.
I would also like to work as a beer vendor.
What is my favorite candy?My favorite candy is, er, I don't know what it is, myself.
But chocolate, you know, that...
There's chocolate cookies.
They're chocolate chip cookies.
I like the ones that come in those boxes, the ones they sell in the supermarket.
What is your favorite part?
A. Also, um...
I like the fact that you met Northeast Iginari and you like him now.
I like the fact that you like me now.
Thank you.
What do you want me to fix?
Huh? Hmmm...
What do you want me to fix? Huh? Um...
What do you want fixed?
What's that?
What do you want me to fix?
Well... tears...
Tears... and a weak spot.
Mm-hmm.
You can't see us with your tears.
A word of love, please.
Thank you so much for meeting us.
I really appreciate all of you who accept us no matter what time of day or what kind of people we are.
Please keep up the good work.
Thank you for everything.
What is your ultimate goal as a talker?
Well, of course, I will continue to work as TALK,
I would like to do what each member wants to do individually,
I would like to do something that is derived from TALK.
I would like to work on creating live performances.
What is one word of love you would like to say to the members of TOKU?
They really understand me a lot and are very funny,
I am really happy to be a member of this group.
I will continue to make you laugh and make you laugh, so let's do our best!Keep up the good work because you all make me laugh and make me laugh!
Thanks again!
I'm done! It was pretty difficult.
I answered the questions quickly and easily.
I may regret it later.
I may regret it later, but at this point today, I'd like to share with you my
You know what?
I mean, the answer.
Yes.
I hope you all got to know me.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Now I'm going to ask you 500 questions, 500 questions, and I hope you all got to know me.
Please keep in touch with me.
I'm going to do 500 questions this time.
Okay, bye-bye!
Bye!